Be afraid of what lies beneath...
The Bridge is a documentary film directed by Eric Steel.
The Bridge is a controversial documentary that shows people jumping to their death from the
Golden Gate Bridge in San Francisco - the world's most popular suicide destination.
Interviews with the victims' loved ones describe their lives and mental health.
Self, played by Eric Geleynse.
Self, played by Susan Ginwalla.
Self, played by Caroline Pressley.
Self, played by Gene Sprague.
Self, played by Elizabeth 'Lisa' Smith.
Self, played by Rachel Marker.
The Bridge is a 2006 documentary film by Eric Steel spanning one year of filming at the Golden Gate Bridge which crosses the Golden Gate
entrance to San Francisco Bay, connecting the city of San Francisco, California to the Marin Headlands of Marin County, in 2004.
The film shows a number of suicides, and features interviews with family and friends of some of the identified people who
had thrown themselves from the bridge that year and one person who had jumped previously and survived.
The film was inspired by a 2003 article titled "Jumpers",
written by Tad Friend for The New Yorker magazine.
The film crew shot almost 10,000 hours of footage, recording 23
of the known 24 suicides off the bridge in 2004.
The film explores themes of dying and death, suicide, san
francisco, california, suicide attempt, jumping.